export const quizQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What does '¿A cómo tienes [objeto]?' mean?",
      options: [
        "How are you?",
        "What are you charging for [object]?",
        "Where are you?",
        "How much do you want [object]?"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "What are you charging for [object]?",
    },
    {
      question: "Translate 'A lo mejor' to English.",
      options: [
        "Probably",
        "Maybe",
        "Certainly",
        "Definitely"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Maybe",
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'Acercarse a alguien' mean?",
      options: [
        "To say goodbye",
        "To go up to someone",
        "To ignore someone",
        "To call someone"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "To go up to someone",
    },
    {
      question: "Translate 'Amigo/a con derechos' to English.",
      options: [
        "Close friend",
        "Friend with benefits",
        "Best friend",
        "Coworker"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Friend with benefits",
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'Culear' mean?",
      options: [
        "To chat",
        "To dance",
        "To have sex",
        "To eat"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "To have sex",
    },
    {
      question: "Translate 'Fresa' to English.",
      options: [
        "Fruit",
        "Strawberry",
        "Snobby person",
        "Sweet"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Snobby person",
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'Mamar gallo' mean?",
      options: [
        "To tell jokes",
        "To have a good time",
        "To have a laugh",
        "To suck up to someone"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "To have a laugh",
    },
    {
      question: "Translate 'Pisto' to English.",
      options: [
        "Pizza",
        "Pasta",
        "Money",
        "Puzzle"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Money",
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'Ser pelado/a' mean?",
      options: [
        "To be bald",
        "To be a good person",
        "To be lazy",
        "To be grumpy"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "To be a good person",
    },
    {
      question: "Translate 'Vaina' to English.",
      options: [
        "Vein",
        "Thing",
        "Chain",
        "String"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Thing",
    },
    // Add more questions as needed...
  ];